• Wasp Swarm spell is more effective depending on hero level. Damage is increased by 5% per hero Level. Reduction of ATB value is increased by 2% every 3 levels.<br>
• Hero spawns Hives nearby enemy positions when combat starts. The amount depends on hero's Knowledge.<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Avenger<br>
<color_bright>• Natural Magic<br>
<color_default>• Imbue Arrow<br>