Witch Queen
<body_bright>

At the start of combat, the hero casts Slow on a random enemy melee creature, and Confusion to a random enemy ranged creature, for free.

Gains an additionnal level up every 5 levels.

<color=orange>The town production of Scouts and Riders is partially replaced by Blood Witches and Shadow Witches. The amount of Scouts replaced by Blood Witches is 5 * Level, and the amount of Riders replaced by Shadow Witches is equal to hero level.<color_default>