Ring Leader
<body_bright>

At the start of combats, the smallest stack of unupgraded Druids in hero's army is upgraded to Druids of the Council.

Druids of the Council cast Channeling (give their Spellpower to the hero) and Mana Feed (give their mana to the hero if the hero has missing mana) when they arrive.

All Druids in the hero's army get 100% ATB after each turn of the hero during combat.

<color=orange>At the end of the adventure stage, new Druids join hero's army. Their amount is equal to hero level.<color_default>