Rune Artist
<body_bright>

• Chances of success with Fine Rune skill (to not consume resources when activating a rune) are increased by 20% + 1% per hero level (base is 30%).

• Learn a new Runic spell every week, and for all Runic spells learnt, the hero gains +1 to all primary attributes and learns a random spell of the same tier.

• Starts with artifact Rune of Flame, giving +2 Spellpower and a random Runic spell.