This creature can set a snare, invisible to the enemy, on the battlefield. When an enemy falls into the snare, it has a chance to lose some of its original movement range (50%) or even come to a halt (25%). If the snare misfires (25%), the ATB value of the creature that has set it will be set to 0. The above % chances only apply if the enemy (Tier+Stack size/Weekly growth) approaches the same value as the amount of Trappers/25. Otherwise those chances are increased or decreased by 5% for every 25 missing or additional Trappers.