Conqueror <color=yellow>Magic
<br><body_bright>
• Victories provide hero bonus Experience and Golds based on the value of defeated army.<br>
• When standing in an Inferno town's gate at the start of the day, the hero can complete a building for Golds. Wood and Ore are converted to 250 Golds each, and other resources to double this value. Maximum cost increases with hero level.<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Gating<br>
<color_bright>• Governance<br>
<color_default>• Gear Up<br>