Maximus is undoubtedly the strangest knight throughout the Empire. His grandfather, a slave trader orc who served in the Holy Empire, refused to follow the crusades Kunyak orcs. The great liberator respected his choice and spared his life, but he broke his legs. Given the poor reputation of his family among the other orcs, Maximus knew he could never join his people or in the steppes and in the islands, so I decided to find his place in the Empire, first as a servant, then as an elderly landowner gentleman, a wise man who recognized his talents. The most decisive moment of his life was the big tournament Falcon Reach. The Emperor had promised to grant the status of knight and lands who beat in the tournament. Maximus defeated all his rivals and his popularity grew with each of the fighting. At the end of the tournament, was proclaimed as "the greatest" and the Emperor had no choice but to grant him the promised reward. Since then, Maximus served with loyalty to the Empire.