Orlando is more than merely another Demonlord.  When Agrael betrayed the Demon Sovereign and Biara was sent away to cripple the Griffin Empire and its allies, Orlando was the faithful servant that Kha-Beleth sent to foment unrest and recruit worshippers among the Necromancers, Wizards, and Free Cities. Sleazily charismatic and seductively brutal, Orlando has risen to a position of trust and power in the savage hierarchy of Sheogh.