These mighty fiends are summoned from the darkest depths of the demonic realms. They are skilled both in close combat and offensive magic. Pit Lords carry a Vorpal Sword, its dark power instantly killing any creature unlucky enough to be struck by it.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
Empowered Fireball (expert) (28)
Mass Rupture (expert) (16)

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None