Tawny Trainer
<body_bright>

All Rakshasas in hero's army activate their Warm-Up ability at the start of combat, increasing their initiative by 50% for 3 turns.

Every 10 levels, the hero builds or upgrades the Silver Pavillon in a player's Academy town, regardless of the building's prerequisites.
If there is nothing to build, add Rakshasas in hero's army instead. The amount is equal to Level * Number of Academy towns.

Hero has access to the Training skill that gives battle bonuses to Rakshasas.