Reanimator
<body_bright>

The Raise Dead spell has increased effect. The spellpower of this spell is increased by 3 + Level/3.

<color=orange>The amount of Skeletons, Zombies and Ghosts recruits in town is increased by 3 weekly growths, plus 1 per difficulty level.<color_default>

After learning 3 perks in the Necromancy skill, upgrades the Necromancy skill to absolute mastery, that grants more dark energy and raises more creatures after battles.