In the most impenetrable reaches of Irollan live the Dryads. These secretive creatures rarely make themselves visible to others, choosing instead to devote all of their time to the mighty trees that they serve. With the help of their magic, a gift from nature, the dryads are able to heal any plant. This is why they are so worshipped by the treants, whose wounds are treated by the kind Nymphs. Out of gratitude to the Dryads, the trees bless them with the health of the forest.