Unique Ranger's skill. Allows Ranger to choose 2 favored enemies from the Avenger's Guild in any Sylvan town (selecting an initial creature will cover it's upgrades as well). All Ranger's troops will receive a 40% chance to inflict a critical hit upon that creature, giving double damage to it. Before choosing a creature as a favored enemy, the Ranger must kill two whole populations of those creatures.