Archbishop - <color=yellow>Saint
<br><body_bright>
• When an enemy hero casts any spell, there is a chance that this spell fails and gets blocked for the rest of the combat. The probability increases with hero level.<br>
• Build or upgrade the Monastery in the town where the hero is recruited.<br>
• Convert a Peasant in hero's army into a Priest after every victory.<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Courage<br>
<color_bright>• Light Magic<br>
<color_default>• Master of Abjuration<br>