These birds of pure fire roam freely in the skies. They are powerful allies for any hero lucky enough to find their hidden lairs and enlist their support. The essence of fire makes Phoenixes very hard to hit - any attacking creature will burn in their flames. But the most amazing Phoenix ability is to rise anew from the ashes they burn down to after their death.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None