Necromancers who wish to cheat death become Vampires with ever-youthful -- but empty -- bodies. Any damage that Vampires inflict upon the living heals their own immortal forms. Gifted with hundreds of years of combat experience, they are so swift with their swords than none can retaliate against their strikes.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None