Battle Commander
<body_bright>

Creatures in hero's army have a 40% + 1% per hero level bonus to their ATB at the start of combat.

Hero uses Ralling Cry to boost army Morale and rage points every turn during combat.

After every victory, gain an amount of any orc creatures that have participated in the battle. The amount is equal to 1.5 * Level / (Tier * (Tier+1)) (rounded down). Hence the minimum level required for each creature tier is 2 (T1), 4 (T2), 8 (T3), 14 (T4), 20 (T5) and 38 (T7).