ArchBishop - <color=yellow>Saint
<br><body_bright>
• When an enemy hero casts any spell, there is a chance that this spell fails and gets blocked for the rest of the combat. The probability increases with hero level.<br>
• Build or upgrade the Monastery in the town where the hero is recruited. If already built and upgraded, add Priests to recruit.<br>
• Convert 1% of Peasants in hero's army to Priests after every victory (minimum 1).<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Courage<br>
<color_bright>• Light Magic<br>
<color_default>• Aura of Energy<br>