The Legendary Dragon rises from the bones of fallen empires, its golden hide etched with the scars of wars it never lost. Its roar shakes the roots of mountains, and its gaze turns armies to ash before they draw steel. Kings kneel not in surrender, but in awe, for it is not merely a beast, but the last judgment of fire and fury given form.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None