This creature has a chance to frighten a target and its neighbors by the attack (small creatures are more disposed to fear). In the event of success the attacker gets +1 to it's Morale and +10% to it's Health. The chance is based on the creature's own Hit Points (HP), considering the entire stack. If the target's HP is lower after the hit those odds are equal to 40% + (5% * (HP/TargetHP)). If target's HP is higher, then 40% - (5% * (TargetHP/HP)).