Born Saifiros, "sharp steel eyes", in one of the smaller kingdoms of Irollan, this master con artist changed her name to "Sephinroth" because she felt it sounded more exotic and regal, giving her an aura of mystery. A skillful liar, she tried to pass herself as the late King Arniel's illegitimate daughter, hoping it would help her secure a place at Vaniel’s court. She even tried to persuade the new king that marrying her would be the key to pacify a land torn apart by civil war. As the lies were becoming bigger and bolder, Sephinroth eventually made a mistake, a single slip of the tongue at the worst possible moment, and the whole deception crumbled on itself. The authorities hot on her trail, Sephinroth managed to escape and hide among the exiled Dark Elves. Because any lie she could say would instantly be foiled by Malassa's whispers, Sephinroth discovered with delight that, in the underground realm, she could be a character she hadn’t have any opportunity to play in a long, long time: herself.