Draconic Prophet
<body_bright>

<color=orange>Hero has a chance to get a random artifact from the Dragon set every time he levels up. The probability is equal to 10% + 1% per level.<color_default>

<color=orange>The effect of the Dragon set does not summon Legendary Dragons but it increases the largest dungeon dragon stack by 1 instead.<color_default>

<color=orange>At the end of the adventure stage, if the hero has 4 dragon artifacts equipped, 6 Cave Dragons join his army. If he has 6 dragon artifacts then it is 16 dragons instead. If he has all 8 dragon artifacts then it is 26 Cave Dragons.<color_default>

After learning 3 perks in the Arcanism skill, upgrades the Arcanism skill to absolute mastery, that increases elemental chain damages and ignoring 100% of enemy magic-proof.