Jeddite was a powerful magician with an affinity with the Magic of Fire. His love for the objects on fire became an obsession to the point that the rest of magicians began to consider him dangerous. It was not long until he entered the service Jeddite Abaddon the Demon Lord of Destruction. One day, staring as the fire consumed the tower of his master (with his teacher still inside), Jeddite was assaulted by a vision of a knight in armor blazing. This was presented as Kha-Beleth, the Prince without throne and told him he had dropped plans for the magician. Kha-Beleth to Jeddite away from the path of want on destruction, and became the herald of older designs. It is rumored that this time Jeddite could see what was hidden under the helmet of Kha-Beleth, but has always refused to comment on this rumor. Now is raising a secret society of Chaos worshipers in the Seven Cities.