Warchief of the Whitespear Clan from Redskull Island, Kraal proudly traces his lineage back to the first Orc tribes who rebelled against heir Wizard creators and have wandered Ashan, rootless, ever since. A wily, tenacious leader, Kraal is unshakable in his belief that, as Father Sky has decreed, his clan is entitled to the harsh, mountainous lands where they currently reside – lands that form part of the Griffin Duchy. Slava, the Duke of Griffin, considers him as his friend, and asked him to become the master-of-arms of his five children. Caught in the middle of bitter enmities that exist between House Griffin and House Wolf, Kraal has become a skilled player in diplomacy, but hides this well by playing up to Orc stereotypes of limited intelligence, hot-headedness, and violent tendencies. Dice and other games of chance are his only indulgence.