Djinns are ancient elemental spirits whom the Wizards can summon and magically bind to their person. Once a Djinn is thus bound, he cannot retreat, and will protect his master until all his vital energy is consumed. Djinns are very useful on the battlefield, but their magical essence makes them chaotic and unpredictable. It is impossible to predict which spell a Djinn will use against the enemy, but it is sure, at least, that they won't turn against their friends. Spellcasting is not Djinn’s sole task on the battlefield, as they can also engage in melee with their heavy scimitars.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None