Golems are ancient magical constructs that are used as primary battle units by the Silver Cities. Golems are armed with two long curved swords, and their substance is their armour. Stone golems are impervious to slowing effects - they really can’t get much slower -  and are well protected against magic (all damage from such attacks is halved).

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body_bright><left>
None