Workshop Expert
<body_bright>

Ballista receive +1 to their Attack for every level of the hero.

Ballista start combats with 100% ATB.

Hero wears the Ring of Machine Affinity that improves War Machines efficiency. The Ballista gains 1 additional shot, the First Aid Tent heal is doubled, and the Ammo Cart increases shooters Attack by +4.

<color=orange>Starting army is improved by an additional weekly growth of Defenders and all three War Machines.<color_default>