Elven Sage
<body_bright>

<color=orange>Every 3 levels up<color_default>, hero gains a skill point in one of the known Magic Schools. If none of the Magic Shools is known, then gain 1000 experience points instead. If the hero has already mastered a Magic School at expert level, he gains +1 to one of the primary attributes. Light Magic grants Defense, Dark Magic grants Attack, Destructive Magic grants Spellpower and Natural Magic grants Knowledge.

Hero has a permanent +1 Initiative.