Frost Mage
<body_bright>

Hero casts Ice Bolt on a random ennemy creature each turn in combat (requires mana).

Every day, hero has a small chance to obtain an artifact from the Frozen Kingdom set. The probability is equal to 5% for the Evercold Icicle and the Frozen Heart and 1% for the Crown and Spear of the Frost Lord. This probability is increased by 5% per hero level. You cannot get the same artifact twice.