In times of peace, the Hunters supply the Sylvan communities with food, and they are respected for their skills and prowess. Wandering Irollan, they live in harmony with Nature and its unwritten laws. They will never kill a living being without purpose. In times of war, however, they have no compunction about using their talents to strike down enemies from afar. Their uncanny affinity with their enchanted Elf bow allow them to fire two shots before an enemy can even blink.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body><left>
Basic Training<body_bright><br>
+2 Attack
<body><br>
Advanced Training<body_bright><br>
+2 Attack
+1 Maneuvre
<body><br>
Expert Training<body_bright><br>
+4 Attack
+1 Maneuvre