Lady of the forest
<body_bright>

• Creature's in hero's army start battles with the effect of the Regeneration spell. After a few hero turns in combat, she casts Regeneration on all friendly creatures, replacing the prior permanent Regeneration effect by a temporary one. The amount of turns is 5 + 1 every 5 hero levels.

• Sylvan creatures inflict 10% + 2% per level bonus damage to favoured enemies.