Master of Gating
<body_bright>

The number of creatures called through the Gating increases by 1% per hero level.

Build the Infernal Loom in the town where the hero is recruited. If already built, gain 5000 experience points instead.

After learning 3 perks in the Gating skill, upgrades the Gating skill to absolute mastery, that increases the amount of gated creature and allows to gate Devils.