The dark elves have always respected assassins, but they reserve particular esteem for those killers who are masters of stealth, capable of taking their unsuspecting victims by complete surprise. The finest exponents of this art are the Stalkers. Evading the traps, swords and spells of their foes, the Stalker will slip unseen past any guard in order to deliver the fatal blow to his target.

<h3><center>Spells
<body_bright><left>
None

<h3><center>Training bonuses
<body><left>
Basic Training<body_bright><br>
+1 Speed
<body><br>
Advanced Training<body_bright><br>
+1 Speed
Incorporeal
<body><br>
Expert Training<body_bright><br>
+3 Attack
+1 Speed
Incorporeal