Exhauster
<body_bright>

• Enemy units have their Speed reduced by 1 and their Initiative reduced by 1% per hero level.

• Opponent hero has 0 Initiative until first hero turn. Also remove the bonus to starting ATB of enemy hero.

• Gain artifacts from the Afterlife set by reaching certain levels. Level 7 for the Tunic of Carved Flesh, level 11 for the Cursed Ring, level 19 for the Spirit of Oppression, level 23 for the Deadwood Staff, and level 29 for the Skull Mask.