• All Scouts in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defence for every two levels of the hero.<br>
• Scouts in hero's army act first in combat.<br>
• The hero generates an amount of golds per day for each Scout in his army. The amount is 1 per 5 levels of the hero, starting at level 5.<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Arcanism<br>
<color_bright>• Logistics<br>
<color_default>• Pathfinding<br>