+1 Attack if equipped<br>
+K/2 Ore per week<br><color_default>
(K=Knowledge of the hero, for example 10 Ore per week for 20 Knowledge)<br><br><color=orange>
Cornucopia<color_default><br>Collect one artifact for every resource type (except gold) and visit an Arcane Library for a unique reward.<br><br><color=yellow>
Backpack<color_default><br>
Resources are also gained when the artifact is in the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per resource type per hero.