Governor of the Mines
<body_bright>

Flame Lords and Thunder Thanes cast their special ability on random enemy creatures at the start of combat.

Every new week, Dwarven Workers are added in garnison of player's resource generating buildings. The amount is 10 + 2 * Level in each building.

Dwarven Workers increase the daily production of resources by 1% per worker in the building (rounded down, up to 400%). When garnisoned in a town, they increase the daily Gold income by 2 per unit and the weekly production of Thanes by 1 per 100 units.