Urghat has been nicknamed both "the Invisible" and the "the Relentless". A hunter from her earliest days, her skills in tracking and traveling meant that her clan never went hungry. During the brutal cold of the Year of the Long Frost she not only slew many Yetis who prowled the winter camps in search of food, but she also tracked one for six days through snow and ice back to its pack where she spent the next week killing off the other thirty-seven members. 