Fortress Protector
<body_bright>

All Defenders in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero.

Defenders in hero's army gain +1 HP for every 10 levels of the hero.

<color=orange>At the end of the adventure stage, new Defenders join hero's army. Their amount is equal to 12 * Level.<color_default>

After learning 3 perks in the Runelore skill, upgrades the Runelore skill to absolute mastery, that removes Wood and Ore cost for activating runes.