Arch Bishop
<body_bright>

When an enemy hero casts any spell, there is a chance that this spell fails and gets blocked for the rest of the combat. The probability increases with hero level.

Build or upgrade the Monastery in the town where the hero is recruited. If already built and upgraded, add Priests to recruit. The amount is equal to twice the number of weeks passed.

Convert 1% of Peasants in hero's army to Priests after every victory (minimum 1).