Pale Rider
<body_bright>

All Black Knights in hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero.

A new Black Knight joins the hero's army every week.

The hero resurrects Black Knights that died in combat. The maximum amount is 1% of the original stack size per hero level (rounded up).

After learning 3 perks in the Necromancy skill, upgrades the Necromancy skill to absolute mastery, that grants more dark energy and raises more creatures after battles.