Goblin Witch-Doctors are greatly respected among their kin. Renowned for their vast experience and intelligence, these shamans know how to play the tambourine, dance around the fire and tell terrifying stories. They can also torment any foes who try to use magic against them, and there is nothing more unpleasant for a magician than seeing that his spell does not work, or it is not doing what it is supposed to.