The council of warlords promotes only the finest of the finest Slayers to the rank of Chieftain. To earn this title, a Slayer must have survived many battles and offered clear proof of his undying loyalty to the clan and his excellence as a leader. Warriors will follow a chieftain without hesitation, in the knowledge that, under his command they will achieve the stuff of legends, and earn eternal glory.