Avatar of Death - <color=yellow>Reaver
<br><body_bright>
• The hero summons a mysterious creature upon the battlefield to fight on his side. The creature's power depends on the hero's level and spellpower.<br>
• If the creature dies, enemy creatures are sorrowed and hero loses all his mana.<br>
• Builds the Dragon Tombstone in the town where the hero is recruited.<br>
<br>
<color_header>Starting Skills<br>
<color_bright>• Necromancy<br>
<color_bright>• Learning<br>
<color_default>• Intelligence<br>