Semi-God
<body_bright>

There is a higher chance that enemy spells redirected by the Magic Mirror skill land on one of the enemy units instead of going in a random direction.

After every victory, an additional free Djinn joins hero's army, and each dead Djinn can be respawned using 10 Mana. The total Mana cost of the resurrection is reduced by 1 for every Djinn remaining in the army.

Djinns in hero's army generate Gold every day equal to the hero level.